<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Shane&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://gunn3r1995.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Shane&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://gunn3r1995.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Books</title>
      <link>https://gunn3r1995.github.io/top/books/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gunn3r1995.github.io/top/books/</guid>
      <description>The Martian 
Author: Andy Weir Reference: Weir, A., 2011. The Martian. 1st ed. United States: Crown Publishing. Thoughts: Astonishing book which always kept me turning to the next page. The technically details keeps the story relentlessly precise while Mark Watney&amp;rsquo;s wit and charm always kept me laughing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Updating the Blog using Git Submodules</title>
      <link>https://gunn3r1995.github.io/post/2019-02-10-updatingblogusinggitsubmodules/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gunn3r1995.github.io/post/2019-02-10-updatingblogusinggitsubmodules/</guid>
      <description>Updating the blog using Git submodules In a previous post (Creating the blog) I spoke about a plan to do small copy &amp;amp; paste script of the public folder, and then updating the git repository.
This has changed since then as after a bit of research I found this tutorial Hosting Hugo site on GitHub. This uses Git submodules to allow for easy updating of both the content of the blog and the publishing it to the github pages site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating the blog</title>
      <link>https://gunn3r1995.github.io/post/2019-01-12-creatingtheblog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gunn3r1995.github.io/post/2019-01-12-creatingtheblog/</guid>
      <description>Creating the blog Today I was researching in the best and path of least resistance for creating and hosting this blog.
The easy part was hosting; GitHub pages, it&amp;rsquo;s free and provide full flexibility.
I wanted to use Hugo as it allows for very customisable themes (I could create my own in the future). But right now I wanted a quick solution. I could potential use one of them blogging sites like wordpress, but that&amp;rsquo;s boring.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Returning Negative and Positive Numbers</title>
      <link>https://gunn3r1995.github.io/post/2019-01-11-stickfeeditems/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gunn3r1995.github.io/post/2019-01-11-stickfeeditems/</guid>
      <description>Returning Negative and Positive Numbers Abstract Due to the calculations of a piece of work I required to do the following check [Appear Date] &amp;gt;= DateTime.Now.AddDays(-X) where X is the amount of days to add. This determined whether the item supplied should be &amp;lsquo;sticky&amp;rsquo; and therefore at the top of a feed or not.
For Example:
10/01/2019 13:00:00 &amp;gt;= (11/01/2019 14:57:37 - 3 Days) == true; // Sticky 05/01/2019 13:00:00 &amp;gt;= (11/01/2019 14:57:37 - 3 Days) == false; // Not Sticky  However, for readability I wanted X the number of days to be sticky to be a negative number, even if supplied with a positive number.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to Shane&#39;s Blog</title>
      <link>https://gunn3r1995.github.io/post/2019-01-10-firstblog/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gunn3r1995.github.io/post/2019-01-10-firstblog/</guid>
      <description>First Blog This is my first post.
What it is This is going to be my personal blog update on my day-to-day life as a developer, what features and code I implemented, how I did it and what I learned. As well as any useful sources or information found while developing; focusing mainly on the technical aspects.
Why  I want to. Improves my organisation. Helps me remember.  So here goes Today (10/01/2019) I worked on the Feature Notes Builder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://gunn3r1995.github.io/top/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gunn3r1995.github.io/top/about/</guid>
      <description>About me _ShaneSmith&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://gunn3r1995.github.io/top/useful/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gunn3r1995.github.io/top/useful/</guid>
      <description>Useful Productivity //Todo
Development Testing Tools regexr.com An online tool to learn, build, and test Regular Expressions which I constantly use when developing.
Design Tools htmlcolorcodes.com I know there are hundreds of colour picker tools out there but htmlcolorcodes.com has so many useful features. Features like colour harmonies and different shades and tones as well as a simple to use interface and beautiful design. This is always an open tab on my browser when working on websites and applications.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>